https://aluminumboatdocks.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Flotation Systems, Inc. (“FSI”) is devoted in protecting your personal information. With respect to our customers and visitors to our web site, we do not sell, rent, or share any personally identifiable information to outside organizations unassociated with FSI unless required by law.
Information Collected
FSI collects personally identifiable information on a voluntary basis only. Information collected may include; name, street, e-mail address, telephone, etc.. We do not collect any personal information without your knowledge.
Use of Personal Information
FSI may use your personal information to:
Respond to items you request.
Inform you of company information changes.
Inform you of special sales or services.
Inform you of availability of new products or services.
Request feedback on our products and services.
Use of IP Addresses
FSI does not use IP addresses to personally identify users. We do not track any patterns of a particular IP address. We use IP addresses for determining how well each page of our web site performs.
Cookies
FSI may use cookies to acquire non-personal information to improve the users experience on our web site. Cookies are small bits of information that is stored on the users computer when the user visits a web site. Cookies generally store information to remember you when you revisit a web site.
Other Web Site Links
Our web site may include links to other sites. FSI makes every attempt to ensure any links to other sites share high standards and protects your privacy. However, we are not responsible for the information or privacy used by other sites.
Facebook
Twitter
Google
Flotation Systems Aluminum Boat Docks
2700 Alabama Highway 69 South | Cullman
| AL | 35057 | USA
800-711-1785 | info@aluminumboatdocks.com
